[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the title of a 1988 movie starring Richard Dreyfuss:  Moon Over _____", "correct_answer": "Parador", "incorrect_answers": ["Middlesburg", "Paraguay", "Miami"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tiger sharks usually hunt alone.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Lilium plants, commonly known as lilies, are extremely toxic to this animal.", "correct_answer": "Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["Dog", "All of these", "Sheep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The usage of raw sugars, including brown sugar, is not recommended when preparing artificial nectar for Hummingbirds. Why?", "correct_answer": "Raw sugars contain iron.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Raw sugars contain zinc.", "They contain harmful heavy metals."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What useful device was invented by Sylvan Goldman?", "correct_answer": "The shopping cart", "incorrect_answers": ["The TV remote control", "The hair curler", "TiVo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Superbad, Seth ended up getting an outfit from Evans dads closet for the party they were going to.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor won an Academy Award for portraying Atticus Finch, a character from Harper Lees only novel, who represents the ideal of a lawyer and father.", "correct_answer": "Gregory Peck", "incorrect_answers": ["Humphrey Bogart", "Philip Seymour Hoffman", "Robert Duvall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dog Day Afternoon, Sonnys partner got a bit upset when a reporter made this statement.", "correct_answer": "2 homosexuals were holding up the bank.", "incorrect_answers": ["2 crazed gunmen were holding up the bank.", "2 idiots were holding up the bank.", "2 Vietnam veterans were holding up the bank."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Neil Armstrong stepped on the moon with his right foot on first.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where exactly is the retina of the eye positioned?", "correct_answer": "Its lining the inner surface of the eye.", "incorrect_answers": ["Retina is a synonym of pupil.", "Along the optic nerve.", "Right behind the pupil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the breed of animal created from the crossing of a female lion and a male tiger?", "correct_answer": "Tigon", "incorrect_answers": ["Tigen", "Liger", "Liges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, is Carter a princess?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]